{
    "id": "fe1a7f8ee6c54c7c851c567d143b30fb",
    "title": "Idioms And Phrases Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have a …………………… . to pick with him. The other day he called me a liar.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "nail",
                "bone",
                "tooth"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1311a084a67d48b4aa31f8a1bd09ef06"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was almost blown ……………………. by the wind.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "over",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76917b6450f84ee48957d50dca37c330"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suddenly the barrel of gun powder blew ……………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fc9dc2311c1143ae80198c6e7c490835"
        },
        {
            "question": "He will never listen to us. Why should we waste our ………………… ?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "heart",
                "mind",
                "words",
                "breath"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "ec8aafd88a584ecc9377b14ca020c577"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are …………………  to defeat the enemy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "racing",
                "longing",
                "burning"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a240b852b8a34dbd8ac67e3681498877"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was carried ……………………… by his enthusiasm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "away",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a21bb82bb484e76b445f5fa618a3c68"
        },
        {
            "question": "You hit the nail on the ..................................... when you said that politics is a dirty game.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "toe",
                "trunk",
                "head"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab32b39c8a8b4304a0f40ccd1b2d8625"
        },
        {
            "question": "He never thought that I would hit him in a …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "jiffy",
                "flash",
                "breeze"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1faf025122fb416fa41c7ddb6e5028c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I held my ……………………… when I first saw a tiger in the wildness.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "voice",
                "breath",
                "eyes"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ac25dcaf13ae4fee822cb76564997b85"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was left ………………… and dry when a pickpocket deprived me of all my money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "low",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81cd80baa6cc45be80d28dc36c709a62"
        }
    ]
}